今天是中午的班呀
You work the lunch shift?
是啊  我还带了八磅快坏的鲑鱼回来
Yeah. I've got eight pounds of salmon that's about to go bad.
你知道怎么煮吗
Do you know how to cook it?
-不知道  -该死
- Not really.  - Damn it.
早知道就应该拿那些问题鸡肉
Should have liberated the iffy chicken.
你和那个挑剔鬼今晚有啥节目
What are you and Professor Fussyface up to tonight?
看蓝光版星球大战
Star Wars on Blu-ray.
你们不是已经看了N遍了吗
Haven't you seen that movie, like, a thousand times?
蓝光版的没有啊
Not on Blu-ray.
蓝光的只看了两遍
Only twice on Blu-ray.
可悲啊  莱纳德
Oh, Leonard.
我知道  都是高清惹的祸
I know, it's high-resolution sadness.
我今晚打算去看一场电影
Well, I'm going to take myself out to a movie tonight.
你想去吗
You want to go?
真的吗  我们能去吗
Really? Do we do that?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你也知道  自从咱俩分手以后
You know, we haven't spent time alone together
就没单独出去玩过
since we broke up.
莱纳德  这又不是约会
Oh, it's not a date, Leonard.
只是一个男人和一个女人出去玩
It's just a man and a woman hanging out,
晚上各回各家  各睡各床
not having sex at the end of the night.
这是我大多数约会的真实写照
Sounds like most of my dates.
老天呐  离我远点  你个怪物
Oh, dear Lord, get away from me, you monster!
这是怎么回事
What is that about?
他够聪明也够疯狂
Well, he's smart and crazy enough,
没准真造了个怪物出来
he may have actually created a monster.
去  去  快走
Shoo, shoo! Be gone!
到底是怎么了
What the hell is going on?
窗户外面有只鸟  死活不肯走
There's a bird outside the window, and he won't go away.
弄得我跟人间炼狱似的
That is the hell that is going on.
我们这儿既没虫子也没种子
We have no worms or seeds here.
去去  快走
Shoo! Shoo!
不是吧  这世界那么险恶  你怕的却是小鸟
Really? On top of everything else, you're afraid of birds?
这叫恐鸟症
It's called ornithophobia.
而且总有一天  恐鸟症会被视为一种残疾
And someday it will be recognized as a true disability,
房东必须按照法律规定
and the landlord will be required by law
给这栋楼加一张大网
to put a giant net over the building.
到时就悲剧了  因为我还怕网
Which is unfortunate, because I have a fear of nets.
电影  你去不去
So movies, yes or no?
去  一定去
Movies, yes.
好  待会儿见
Great. I'll see you later.
记住啦  他其实比你还害怕呢
And remember, he's more afraid of you than you are of him.
说这话一点用都没有
That doesn't help.
谁跟你说了  我跟鸟说呢
No, I was talking to the bird.
小鸟快走  小鸟快走  小鸟快走
Go away, bird. Go away, bird. Go away, bird.
谢尔顿  无视它不就行了
Sheldon, just ignore him.
好主意  这鸟无非就是求关注
Good idea. Attention is what birds want.
啊  好多了  好
Oh, much better. All right.
我现在可以安心了
Now I'll just get along with my life.
泡壶茶  莱纳德  今晚要跟它抗争到底了
Make a pot of tea, Leonard. It's going to be a long night.
那鸟还没走呢
The bird's still there?
快  老鹰是怎么叫的
Quick, what does a hawk sound like?
我也不太清楚
I don't know--
拜托  那是海鸥的声音
Please, that's a seagull.
你要是帮不上忙  就闭嘴
If you're not going to help, don't help.
对不起  我穿得会不会太正式了
Sorry. Do you think I'm overdressed?
这得看场合了
It depends on the activity.
如果去做前列腺检查  是有点正式
For a prostate exam, yes.
但如果是扮维加斯  我会加一些亮片
If you're playing Vegas, I'd add sequins.
我是要跟佩妮去看电影
I'm going to the movies with Penny.
我不想让她认为  我认为是约会
I don't want her to think that I think it's a date.
你认为是约会吗
Do you think it's a date?
不  但她会认为我是这么认为
No, but she might think I think it's a date
但其实我不是
even though I don't.
说不定是你认为她认为你这么认为
Or you might think she thinks you think it's a date
其实她不是
even though she doesn't.
-我们是不是想太多了  -绝对没有
- Are we overthinking this?  - Not at all.
你说得对  算了  我就这么穿吧
You're right. I'm fine. I'm wearing this.
不是吧  西装?  好吧
Really? A blazer? All right.
喂  你好
Yes, hello.
我是谢尔顿·库珀博士
This is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
我住在罗夫莱斯北大街2311号
I'm at 2311 North Robles Avenue.
我这里有一只危险的野生动物
I'd like to report a dangerous wild animal.
一只蓝冠鸦
A blue jay.
不好意思  我找的就是动物管理部门
I'm sorry, this is Animal Control.
我不明白你笑什么
I don't understand the laughter.
不  那只鸟不在我家里
No, the bird is not in my home.
它要是在我家里  我早就打911报警了
If he was in my home, I obviously would have called 911.
先生  我相信你也有害怕的东西
Sir, I have no doubt that there are things that you're frightened of.
比如从事没前途的公共服务工作
Being stuck in a dead-end public service job.
或者你老婆背叛你
Or your wife stepping out on you
因为你从事的是没前途的公共服务工作
because you're stuck in a dead-end public service job.
又或者你怕蜘蛛
Or spiders.
学猫叫有用的话  打电话给你干嘛
Don't you think I tried making cat noises?
会不会太休闲了
Too casual?
去觐见女王的话  是太休闲了
For an audience with the queen, yes.
不过晚上去着火的垃圾箱旁边
For an evening of passing a bottle of fortified wine
扔一瓶烈酒  你的着装正合适
around a flaming trash can, you look great.
我想啥呢  居然没画胡子
What am I thinking? Whiskers.
现在买票的话  能赶上珍妮弗·安妮斯顿的新电影
Oh, hey, if we hurry, we can make the new Jennifer Aniston movie.
对  没错
Oh, yeah, sure.
不过还有一场精彩的纪录片
There's also an amazing documentary
讲述在南美洲的一条河上建一座水坝
about building a dam on a river in South America.
可珍妮弗·安妮斯顿的电影里有珍妮弗·安妮斯顿
Okay, but the Jennifer Aniston movie has Jennifer Aniston,
而且她不会建什么水坝
and she's not building a dam.
这倒是真的
Can't argue with that.
-我去买票  -好
- I'll get the tickets.  - Okay.
等等  其实呢
Actually, you know what?
我觉得现在该我挑电影了
I think it's about time I picked a movie we see.
你都挑过好多次了
You pick plenty of movies.
不  都是你挑的
No. You always picked,
而且每次都一样
and it was always the same.
前面90分钟都在说雨中的海滨别墅
An hour and a half of beach houses in the rain
最后女主角顿时醒悟
until the woman turns around
发现原来爱一直在身边
and realizes love was here all along.
拜托  那电影很棒  而且还有10分钟就开演了
Come on, that is a great movie, and it starts in ten minutes.
我讨厌这种电影
I hate those movies.
-你不讨厌  -我真的讨厌
- No, you don't.  - Yes, I do.
我之所以以前和你一起看  是因为你想看
The only reason I went is because you wanted to see them,
而我想和你滚床单
and I wanted to have sex.
而今天  我既然不能兴奋和性奋
To this day, I can't see a Sandra Bullock movie poster
还看什么桑德拉·布洛克的电影啊
without getting both bored and aroused.
好吧  这么说我们约会的时候
Okay, so while we were going out,
你有多少次是假装听我的
how often would you pretend
其实只是为了和我滚床单
to like things just to have sex with me?
一直都是
All the time.
不是吧
You're kidding.
那你觉得这些话耳熟不
Does this sound familiar?
我喜欢和你去逛街买鞋子
I'd love to go shoe shopping with you.
远足  棒极了
Hiking? It's great.
凌晨2点啊  我当然想去
It' 2 a.m., of course I want to go
韩国城和你们朋友唱K啦
to Korea Town and sing karaoke with your friends.
乐意之极
Who wouldn't?
好吧  我们每次约会
Okay, we were going out.
-那次没有滚床单的  -是吗
- You were going to get sex anyway. - Really?
你要是看了三小时水坝的纪录片  你还有性致吗
You would have slept with me after a three-hour documentary on dams?
没有  没女人会有
No. No woman would.
瞧  这就是最棒的地方
See? Now, that's the great thing.
我们现在是朋友  不是在约会
We're out as friends. This is not a date.
滚床单没戏
Sex is off the table.
所以  我们就去看看水力发电
So, let's go learn how hydroelectric power
也许不是你想的那么环保
might not be the environmental bargain you think it is.
抱歉  剧透了
Sorry. Spoiler alert.
好吧
All right, fine.
谢了
Thanks.
电影票十一块
Tickets are 11 bucks.
不是约会嘛
Not a date.
快点  谢尔顿  来看《星球大战》
Come on, Sheldon, Star Wars.
我要按播放键啦  我说真的
I'm pushing play. I mean it.
要是我们再不快点看
If we don't start soon,
乔治·卢卡斯又要出新版本了
George Lucas is going to change it again.
要是你那职业学校的学历有点用
This would go a lot faster
就过来帮我倒腾一下这台高音频发生器
if you put your trade school diploma to work
那我们的问题就解决了
and helped me set up this high-frequency tone generator.
我可是麻省理工的硕士生
I have a Masters degree from M.I.T.
好吧  你好歹有乐观苦干的态度
Yeah, but you've got a can-do attitude
这才是重点
and that's what's important.
我真不懂你和鸟有什么仇
I really don't get your problem with birds.
你该这么问  鸟对我有什么仇
The question you should be asking is what is their problem with me?
我刚开始记事起  一只蜂鸟俯冲进我的婴儿车
My first memory: A hummingbird dive-bombing my stroller
偷吃了我吸管杯里的苹果汁
to get at the apple juice in my sippy cup.
蜂鸟很美的
Hummingbirds are pretty.
蜂鸟是鲜花界的吸血鬼
Hummingbirds are the vampires of the flower world.
还是我在脚踝纹身图案的首选
Still my first choice for an ankle tattoo.
或是海豚  我在这两者间犹豫不决
Or a dolphin-- I go back and forth.
我7岁时  一只丧心病狂的鸡追着我爬到树上
Age seven, a blood-thirsty chicken chases me up a tree.
12岁时  一只喜鹊想从我嘴里抢走牙套
Age 12, a magpie tries to steal the retainer out of my mouth.
16岁时  宠物店的一只鹦鹉骂我胖仔
Age 16, a parrot in a pet store calls me fat ass.
我还要继续说吗
Need I go on?
当然  这可比电影有趣多了
Yes, please. This is way better than the movie.
好吧  谢尔顿
All right, Sheldon,
你的"杀鸟死光"准备好了
your bird death ray is ready.
这不是"死光"
It's not a death ray.
只是弄点超声波好吓跑他
It's just a little ultrasonic blast to scare him off.
相信我  如果我有"死光"
Trust me, if I had a death ray,
我就不会住这儿了
I wouldn't be living here.
我会坐在用不完的钱堆上
I'd be in my lair enjoying the money
都是人们送来贿赂我求我别用"死光"
the people of Earth gave me for not using my death ray.
好吧  三
All right, and in three,
二  一
two, one.
这只小鸟真霸气
That is one tough birdie.
拜托  你明明很喜欢那电影
Come on, you enjoyed the movie.
村庄要被淹没  所有人要搬家时
I saw you tearing up when the village got flooded,
我看你都哭了
and everyone had to relocate.
不  我是想为什么他们能走而我不行
No, I was thinking how come they get to leave and I can't.
我去买点薯条
I'm going to get some fries.
你要来点吗
You want anything?
-不  谢了  -你确定吗
- Uh, no, thanks.  - Are you sure?
你每次都说不要  却把我的吃掉一半
You always say no, and then you eat half my fries.
我只是吃那些酥脆的  反正你不喜欢
I just eat the little crispy ones you don't like.
不  我超喜欢  我只是留到最后吃
No, I love them. I save them for the end,
结果却被你吃光光
but they're gone because you ate them.
我为什么让你吃呢
And why did I let you eat them?
-你想滚床单  -没错
- To get sex.  - Exactly.
但这不是约会
But this is not a date.
所以我再问一次  你要来点什么吗
So I ask again, would you like anything?
好吧  给我来份薯条
All right, I'd like an order of fries.
好极了  五块钱
Great. That'll be five dollars.
这是我有史以来最开心的夜晚
I am having the best time.
我真高兴你约我出来
I'm so glad you suggested we do this.
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
没关系
No problem.
你在写什么
What you writing there?
剧本
A screenplay.
叙述的是一个宅男的室友因为要打炮
It's about a guy whose roommate is having sex
所以把他赶来酒吧写剧本的悲惨故事
and tells him to go to a bar and work on his screenplay.
电影名《我希望艾力克斯染上阴虱》
"I Hope Alex Gets Crabs: The Movie."
这只是暂定名
It's a working title.
-我叫凯文  -我叫佩妮
- I'm Kevin.  - Oh. Penny.
幸会幸会
Nice to meet you.
我就不打扰你们约会了
I'll let you get back to your date.
不不  我们没在约会  完全不是
Oh, no, no. This isn't a date, no.
对吧
Right?
对
Uh... right.
那你的作品有没有我可能看过的呢
So have you written anything I might have seen?
不好说  你喜欢逛大众点评网吗
That depends. How much time do you spend on Yelp?
真是太傻了
This is ridiculous.
我都是个来自德州的成年人了
I'm a grown man from Texas.
这鸷鸟肯定不像天鹅和家鹅那么吓人
This isn't a terrifying bird like a swan or a goose.
一只蓝松鸦而已
It's just a blue jay.
还是只挺大的蓝松鸦
That's a pretty big blue jay.
一
One...
二
Two...
三
Three.
去去  死鸟  快走开
Go! Shoo! Am-scray, ird-bay!
鸟飞进屋子了
Bird in the apartment!
不要啊
No!
这部纪录片太赞了
So it is an amazing documentary.
他们急需建座大坝来发电  但同时
They need the electricity from the dam, but at the same time,
他们也想保护环境
they want to preserve the environment.
真会过河拆桥呀
You're kidding me.
你能稍微过来一下吗
Uh, can I see you for a sec over here?
当然可以  等我一下哦
Oh, yeah. Sure. Just one sec?
没问题
No problem.
有事吗
What's up?
-我知道你在耍什么小把戏  -耍什么
- I know what you're doing. - What am I doing?
你千方百计地勾搭那哥们儿聊天
You're going out of your way to talk to that guy
就因为我说咱俩没在约会
because I said we weren't on a date.
才没有  我跟他聊是因为他很帅
No, I'm talking to him because he's cute.
-拜托  他哪有那么帅  -不  他就是很帅
- Come on, he's not that cute. - Yes, he is.
看那件傻傻的T恤和那副潮潮的小眼镜
With his dorky T-shirt and his little hipster glasses.
我也穿傻傻的T恤  也戴着小眼镜
I wear dorky T-shirts and glasses.
是呀  等你个子和颧骨都高点再说吧
Yes, but when you're tall and have great cheekbones,
你现在就是人家的反面教材
you're doing it ironically.
如果这样的话  要是我也去跟女孩子聊天呢
If that's so, what if I start talking to a girl?
快去啊
You should!
我是说真的  我真去哦
I'm serious. I'll do it.
去啊  快去啊  那边有好几个漂亮妹子
Good! Go! There are some girls right over there.
你怎么还不冲过去
What are you waiting for?
她们人好多  我好怕怕
They're in a group. I'm scared.
谢尔顿  你指望我俩来干啥
Sheldon, what do you expect us to do?
你是生物学家
You're biologists.
生物就是研究生物的
Biology is the study of living things.
那就是个生物  开始研究吧
That's a living thing; get cracking.
我是搞微生物学的
I specialize in microorganisms,
艾米是研究大脑的
and Amy studies brains.
对啊  我俩都没辅修过如何赶鸟
Yeah, neither of us minored in bird-shooing.
拜托
Oh, come now.
你们在本科的时候肯定学过
Your undergraduate work must have included
如何对付讨人嫌的小动物
a varmints and critters class.
进来吧  谢尔顿  他不会伤害你的
Come back in, Sheldon, he's not going to hurt you.
他看上去好和善的
He looks friendly.
我觉得他没准儿是谁家的宠物
I think he might be someone's pet.
不要  伯纳黛特  别逞英雄
No, Bernadette, don't be a hero!
他真可爱
Oh, he's a sweetie.
对  很可爱
Yes. It's very sweet.
好  现在慢慢地  小心地
Now, slowly and carefully,
把他丢到厕所里冲走
flush him down the toilet.
谢尔顿  克服这种恐惧的唯一办法
Sheldon, the only way to get past this fear
就是参与进来
is to interact with it.
就像你对付那个邮递员那样
Just like you did with the mailman.
全世界每年都有好几十个人被鸟害死
Every year tens of people around the world are killed by birds.
我不要为这个统计数据作贡献
I'm not going to be another statistic.
你看看他有多可爱  过来打个招呼嘛
Look how sweet he is. Come over and say hi.
来啊
Come on.
你能行的
You can do it.
别怕
Don't be scared.
快来
Come on.
快摸一下  你个胆小鬼
Oh, just pet the bird, you big baby!
我做到了
I did it!
我真的做到了
I actually did it.
好了  可以扔进厕所冲了
Okay, now flush him.
莱纳德  你平时有什么爱好
So, Leonard, what do you do for fun?
我  我想想看哈
I'm... let's see.
远足
Hiking.
去韩国城K歌
Karaoke in Koreatown.
看杰尼佛·安妮斯顿的电影
Any Jennifer Aniston movie.
不好意思刚冷落了你
Hey. Sorry I ditched you.
-没事没事  你去忙你的吧  -没事  不忙了
- No, it's fine. You can ditch away.  - Oh, no, no.
我们说好一起出来玩的嘛  一起玩吧
We said we were going to hang out, let's hang out.
没事  你跟凯文玩吧
It's cool. Go back to Kevin.
他走了
Oh, he had to leave.
有意思
Interesting.
所以现在是他走了  你又想跟我玩了
So now that he's gone, you want to hang out with me.
-这位肯定是佩妮  -对
- This must be Penny.  - Yep.
让我茅塞顿开呀
I totally get it.
不好意思  哪里塞了
Huh? I'm sorry, get what?
你别管了  那边有好几个帅哥哥
Don't worry about it. You know, there's some guys over there.
你去跟他们聊聊呗
You should go talk to them.
不了  我就想知道你跟她说什么了
No, no. I want to know what you told her.
这应该是我和...
That's kind of between me and...
-劳拉  -劳拉之间的秘密吧
- Laura.  - Laura.
好吧  明白了
Oh. Okay, I see.
他跟你聊天时  有没有提到他拥有不止一件
So while he was telling you things,did he mention he owns,
而是两件星际迷航制服呢
not one, but two Star Trek uniforms?
-真的吗  -真的  还经常穿
- Really?  - Yeah. Wears them.
不光万圣节哦
Not just for Halloween.
嘿  伙计
Hey, pal.
我可没告诉凯文
You didn't see me telling Kevin that
你认为冷战只在冬天开战
you thought cold wars were only fought in winter.
好吧  那我就还你人情  不告诉...
Okay. Then I'll return the favor, and I won't tell...
-劳拉  -劳拉
- Laura. ...  - Laura
你收藏的黄片  一半是动画片
that half the dirty movies you own are animated.
你向凯文讲述你的演艺生涯时
When you were telling Kevin about your acting career,
有提到你在本土商家芝士工厂内
did you mention your long-running role as "Waitress"
长期"扮演"女服务生的角色吗
in a local production of The Cheese Factory?
那你告诉了她  你有哮喘了吗
Did you tell her about your lucky asthma inhaler?
是吗  那你说说"哮喘"怎么写
Oh, yeah? Spell "asthma."
都是口字旁...
A-s...
送我回家
Take me home.
我还没跟她聊够呢
Maybe I'm not done hanging out with...
你说得对  太晚了
You're right, it's getting late.
真是奇了怪了
It's remarkable.
我居然怕了这么长时间
All that time spent in fear.
何必呢
And for what?
他真是太美了
He's magnificent.
天啊
Oh, dear.
我刚想起  我还没给你上饮料
I just realized I haven't offered you a beverage.
就像我祖母跟她的鹦鹉一样
Oh, it's just like my grandma with her parrot.
尤其在遥控器不好使后  这么喂还能顺便换台
And after she lost her marbles with her remote control.
我电话在那边桌上
My phone's on the desk over there.
给我们俩拍张照片
Take a picture of us together.
拍好点  我要贴上马克杯  鼠标垫和日历
Make it good enough to go on a mug, a mouse pad, and a calendar.
你要是鸽子  我就叫你爱鸽
If you were a dove, I'd call you Lovey-Dovey.
开什么玩笑
Oh. Who am I kidding?
现在就不该拘泥于字面意思
This isn't a moment for strict adherence to the literal.
你就是我的爱鸽  不是吗
You're just my little Lovey-Dovey, aren't you?
估计你的骨头也是中空的
Guess you gotta have hollow bones
才能承载这么多甜言蜜语
to get some sugar around here.
我还是觉得他是别人家的宠物
I still think he looks like someone's pet.
或许我们该去贴失物招领
Maybe we should put up posters.
对  要附上他的一张大照片
Yes. It should have a big picture of him,
还要写上"这是你的鸟吗  现在成我的了"
and the words, "Is this your bird? Not anymore."
我们在一起肯定会很开心
We're going to have so much fun together.
你可以帮我捎口信给我所有的敌人
You can carry messages to all my enemies.
还可以在你腿上系上绳  像放风筝拽着玩
I can tie a string to your leg and fly you like a kite.
你要想收留他  我可以借你个笼子
If you're keeping him, I've got a cage you can borrow.
那笼子以前关的实验猴  踩到香蕉皮
One of the test monkeys slipped on a banana peel
把脖子摔断了
and broke his neck.
悲剧和喜剧同时上演
It was both tragic and hysterical.
荒谬
Nonsense.
不行  爱鸽才不睡笼子里
No. Lovey-Dovey doesn't sleep in a cage.
爱鸽要睡在他自己的巢里
No. Lovey-Dovey sleeps in his very own nest,
我要把窗台的巢拿下来  放我房间里
which I'm going to get off the windowsill and put in my room.
对不对呀  爱鸽
Isn't that right, LD?
别走呀
No.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
回来  爱鸽
Come back, Lovey-Dovey!
现在这才是你的家
This is your home now!
我已经从亚马逊订了20磅鸟食
I already ordered 20 pounds of bird feed off of Amazon!
他不见了
He's gone.
节哀顺变  谢尔顿
I'm sorry, Sheldon.
他怎么能这么对我呢
How could he do this to me?
回来  笨鸟  不然我的爱给谁去
Get back here, you stupid bird, so I can love you!
好了  我们一起出去了
Okay. So... we went out,
看了电影  认识了不错的人
saw a movie, met some nice people,
公开说了一些彼此的坏话
said horrible things about each other in public...
总而言之  真是个神奇的夜晚
all in all, a pretty magical night.
好吧  这事我也有错
Okay, I'm not innocent in all this,
但你居然说我笨  你个患哮喘的蠢蛋
but you basically called me stupid, you asthmatic dumbass.
我知道  我是过分了
I know, I-I-I crossed a line.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
别走  等等  我是真的很抱歉
No, no, no, hang on. I really mean it.
这并不是像我们以前交往那样
And it's not like when we were going out,
我不是为了跟你滚床单才道歉的
I'd just apologize for everything so we could end up in bed.
这句"我很抱歉"是纯发自内心  与滚床单无关
This is a 100% sex-is-off-the-table "I'm sorry."
好吧  谢谢你
All right. Thank you.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
我再确认下  滚床单没戏  对吧
Just to be clear, sex is off the table, right?
绝对没戏
Way off.
也许我们还没准备好像朋友一样出去玩
Maybe we're not ready to hang out as friends.
我也不知道  其实在事情搞砸之前
I don't know. Up until the last part,
我还是很喜欢管着莱纳德
I was kind of enjoying take-charge Leonard
当他的主心骨
with a little backbone.
我来选电影  我知道他想要什么
Picking the movie, knowing what he wants,
还有点自大
a little cocky.
-真的吗  -真的
- Really?  - Yeah.
好吧  那就是说滚床单有戏咯
Well, then, I'm putting sex back on the table.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think about that?
-或许我会喜欢  -是吗
- Ooh. Maybe I like it. - You do?
真的  要是你喜欢  我可以恢复原样
Because if that's what you like, I can be that guy.
我发誓  你让我往东我绝不往西
I swear, I'll be anything you want me to be.
晚安  莱纳德
Good night, Leonard.
我还真是个患哮喘的蠢蛋
I am such an asthmatic dumbass.
我今晚过得很怪怪的
I had a weird night.
我过得很好
Mine was great.
我要当妈咪了
I'm going to be a mommy!